{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622641","name":"Fresh 101 Superfood Cafe","address":"4240 Cass Ave Ste. 100","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Monique Dooley","licenseNumber":"229262","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.06362,42.35134","geojson":{"id":"51622641","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.063619025,42.3513433890001]},"properties":{"name":"Fresh 101 Superfood Cafe","owner":"Monique Dooley","address":"4240 Cass Ave Ste. 100","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"229262","establishmentid":"51622641","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"7/13/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622479","name":"Tou & Mai","address":"4240 Cass Ste 102","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4608","name":"Go! Sy Thai","address":"4240 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622794","name":"Spread Deli","address":"4215 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5380","name":"Alley Taco","address":"418 Willis St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622811","name":"Avalon International Breads","address":"422 W Willis St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5056","name":"Treat Dreams","address":"4160 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5386","name":"Detroit Royale with Cheese","address":"4163 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4646","name":"La Feria Spanish Tapas","address":"4130 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5042","name":"Slows On The Go Mobile Kitchen","address":"4107 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4152","name":"Slows To Go","address":"4107 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"41368","inspectionDate":"2018-02-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Missing Light Shield(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at 30 inches above the floor","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FOOD SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"At the Light bulb(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room door(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Propped open","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Missing Self-closing device","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Do not prop door open."},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"No Covered waste container","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"41057","inspectionDate":"2017-12-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \r\n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \r\n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \r\n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"violationCode":"3-306.11","violationDescription":"Except for nuts in the shell and whole, raw fruits and vegetables that are intended for hulling, peeling, or washing by the CONSUMER before consumption, FOOD on display shall be protected from contamination by the use of PACKAGING; counter, service line, or salad bar FOOD guards; display cases; or other effective means. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food on display","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lacking protection","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Paper toweling","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate sanitary hand drying aids/devices."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"violationCode":"4-402.12","violationDescription":"Unless otherwise approved, floor-mounted EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be SEALED to the floor or elevated on legs that provide at least a 6 inch clearance between the floor and the EQUIPMENT (COUNTER-MOUNTED equipment that is not easily moveable shall be elevated on legs at least 4 inches high).\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor-mounted equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to floor","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to floor."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"20 foot candles","location":"WAREWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"10 foot candles","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"50 foot candles","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"4-101.19","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT that are exposed to splash, spillage, or other FOOD soiling or that require frequent cleaning shall be constructed of a CORROSION-RESISTANT, nonabsorbent, and SMOOTH material.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wood","subItem":"pine","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622641"}}